# LÊ VĨNH PHÚC

# **WEB DEVELOPER**

## **SUMMARY**

I am an innovative, task-driven professional with three years of experience in Engineering environments in automation industries. I was deep in Web Development for about one year through self-studying and joining Bootcamp Fullstack Developer Course at Cybersoft Academy. By "always willing" attitude, I wish to join a team that allows me to apply all my knowledge and better day by day to be a skilled Fullstack Developer.

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

- Mobile: (+84) 975 085 625
- levinhphuc95@gmail.com
- https://phuclv.netlify.app
- Dist.7, Ho chi Minh City, Viet Nam

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

## **Good At:**

- HTML5, CSS3
- Javascript, ES6
- React JS, Redux, Redux-thunk
- UI libraries: Material-UI, React-Bootstrap, Styled-Component
- Bootstrap 4, SCSS

## **Basic:**

- Node.js, jwt
- MongoDB, MySQL, SQL Server
- Python 3
- Linux (Ubuntu based)
- Photoshop

## Learning:

- Next JS
- GraphQL
- Angular JS

# **OTHER SKILLS**

- Self-study for new Technology.
- Project Management
- Communication

## **PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE**

# **Building Automation Engineer**

Refrigeratrion Electrical Engineering Bach Khoa Co.,Ltd (07/2019 - 02-2021)

- Designing, making Technical Drawings, programming the Building Management System (DDC, Webserver) for pharmaceutical factories, food and beverage factories, commercial buildings
- Developing the Auto Create Report tool and related tools for Automation System using Python 3, SQL Server
- Research and recommend to Sales Director about new products, new suppliers, competitors, market trend.
- Communicating with oversea suppliers for training programs, placing orders

# **Industrial Automation Engineer**

Asia Refrigeration Industry JSC (06/2018 - 07/2019)

- Designing, making Technical Drawings, programming the Automation System for industrial refrigeration system
- Onsite supervising installation work
- Testing and commissioning systems to make sure it probably work before handling over to clients

## **EDUCATION**

## **Bootcamp Fullstack Web Developer**

Cybersoft Academy (10/2020 - 06/2021)

- Learn HTML5, CSS3, JS, ES6, React and Angular 8+ for Frontend Development
- NodeJS, ExpressJS and MongoDB for Back-end Devalopment
- Apply all knowledge through real-life projects

## **Bachelor Of Electrical & Electronics Engineering**

Ho Chi Minh University of Technology (Bach Khoa)

 Major in Industrial Automation, I was learned about designing, setting up, programming for Automation Systems.

#### **PREVIOUS PROJECTS**

## **OnMeeting Landing Page**

FPT Telecom International

- Project Stack: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, jQuery
- Project Link: www.onmeeting.com.vn
- Description: Edit UI, make website better responsive, update website due to client request.

## **E-Learning Web App**

Final Personal Project of Front-End course at Cybersoft Academy

- Project Stack: React, Redux, Axios, Material-UI, Bootstrap 4, Scss
- Project Link: https://elearning-clone.netlify.app/
- Description: This project was built by my self as my final project of Front-end Course at Cybersoft Academy.
- Function:
  - User: Login, Register, sort courses, search courses, subscribe courses
  - Admin: CRUD users, CRUD courses, manage user subscription for courses

# **Cinema Web App**

Final Team Project of Front-End course at Cybersoft Academy

- Project Stack: React, Redux, Redux-thunk, Axios, Material-UI, Slick, Bootstrap 4, Scss
- Project Link: https://tix-movie.netlify.app/
- Description: This project, base on tix.vn design and functions, was built as our team (2 members) final project of Front-end course at Cybersoft Academy. In this project, I was mainly developed the functions of Web App, where my partner mainly build the UI of project.
- · Function:
  - User: Login, Register, booking tickets due to movie/cinema/date/time, user information management, booking history
  - Admin: CRUD users, CRUD movies, set cinema schedules

## **JustOne Web App**

Personal project for tracking learning

- Project Stack: React, Redux, Redux-thunk, Axios, React-Bootstrap, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, JWT
- Project Link: https://justone.netlify.app/
- Description: This project is build based on ideas from To-Do app for learning MERN stack and for my personal use.
- Function: Login, Register, CRUD, tracking learning status (to learn, learning, learned), video shortcut